MAGGIE Tsz-shuen, LAI

Year of Birth: 1995 Gender: Female

Mobile: +1 (416) 997-8797 E-mail: maggie.laitszshuen@gmail.com

City: Scarborough, ON, Canada Postal Code: M1B 5Z2

SUMMARY

Skilled electrical engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering (Electrical Engineering) and 6 years of experience in the designing, assembling and installing, testing and commissioning in electrical spectrum and water treatment process. Accomplished and goal-driven in panel design, load and cable sizing calculation. Expertise in utilizing technical knowledge to provide support, solution and troubleshooting techniques to clients.

Self-disciplined and motivated on studying electrical spectrum and troubleshooting. Strong team member; able to cooperate and motivate others to achieve optimal production while maintaining safety methods and practices. Strong interpersonal and communication skills; able to coordinate with client, colleagues and coworkers.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Sep 2017 – Apr 2023 ATAL Engineering Limited

(Position held last: Project Engineer)

(Position held during 2019 – 2021: Engineer)

(Position held during 2017 – 2019: Graduate Trainee (Electrical Discipline))

- Expertise in various electrical design and installation, including switchboard and switchgear protection, motor starter and control panel, load and cable sizing calculation, etc.
- Manage the construction site and progress, deliver a quality and on-time service and program according to a timed schedule.
- Performed budget control, held cost negotiation with suppliers, and handled procurement
- Liaised with internal quantitative surveyor and safety officer to maintain a smooth project progress
- Liaised with clients, consultants to maintain good engineering quality and sustain the project profit

Jun 2016 – Aug 2016 ATAL Technologies Limited

(Position held last: Trainee)

- Prepare material submission and manage handover and inventory document
- Assist Engineers to design system circuits and perform system demonstration
- Liaised with contactors and consultant in the interface meeting

Oct 2015 – Apr 2016 Jingle Metal Products Company Limited

(Position held last: Data Analyst (Part-time))

- Issued vouchers and ledgers and recorded raw accounting data with MS Office
- Analyzed inter-year expense and income to project future profits
- Liaised with customers and creditors to confirm invoice and statements, and answer their inquiries

EDUCATION

Sep 2022 - present Diploma in Software Engineering Technician

Centennial College, Progress ON, Canada

Sep 2013 - Jun 2017 Bachelor of Engineering (Electrical Engineering)

The University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

MAGGIE Tsz-shuen, LAI

Year of Birth: 1995 Gender: Female

E-mail: maggie.laitszshuen@gmail.com Mobile: +1 (416) 997-8797 Postal Code: M1B 5Z2

City: Scarborough, ON, Canada

RELEVENT ENGINEERING HIGHLIGHTS

2022 - 2023 Design, Supply, Installation, Testing and Commissioning of Lighting and Small Power System at CLP Power Hong Kong Black Point Power Station Unit D2

- Design the lighting and small power system of various building and outdoor areas
- Coordinated with junior colleagues, manage and review their works
- Performed budget control and held price negotiation with different suppliers

2022 - 2023 Uprating of Ha Wong Yi Au Fresh Water Pumping Station

- As a Site Agent, manage the construction site and deliver a quality and on-time service and program
- As an electrical-in-charge, design the motor starter panel and PLC control panel for 380Vac 250kW centrifugal water motor pumps.
- Interrelated with client to achieve their objectives, while maintaining the SHE and quality standards
- Lead a team of engineers and workers of different discipline to develop and complete the design

2021 Provision of Integrated Maintenance Services for Balance of Plant, Electrical, Control and Instrumentation in Black Point, Penny's Bay Power Stations and Castle Peak Power Station

- Instructed labors and sub-contractors to perform periodic inspection and testing
- Design, install and testing and commissioning of instinctively protection system for power generator
- Liaised with different client parties, including project manager, engineer, safety officer and operators

2018 - 2021 Expansion of Tai Po Water Treatment Works and Ancillary Raw Water and Fresh Water Transfer Facilities - Design and Build of New Stream II

- Install, testing and commissioning of 11kV/380V 1500kVA dry-type transformers
- Design, install and testing and commissioning of Low-voltage switchboards (up to 3200A 380Vac) on varies function, including motor starters, ATS and bus coupler etc.
- Supervised varies sub-contractors and suppliers to complete the design, testing and commissioning according to the planned program
- Handled procurement and involve in budget analysis

2017 - 2018Design, Supply, Delivery, Installation, Testing and Commissioning of an On-Site Chlorine Generation Plant (OSCG) at Ngau Tam Mei Water Treatment Works

- Liaised with US supplier and prepare OSCG system process design submission
- Design electrical distribution for OSCG plant system, including motor starter and control panel
- Design building services system to facilitate the OSCG, including electrical and fire service system

SKILLS

Language: Cantonese (Native), English (Fluent), Mandarin (Fluent) Office Tool: Microsoft Office Proficiency, Microsoft Project, Primavera P6

Technical Tool: AutoCAD, Autodesk Revit, DIALux, Microsoft Visual, Microsoft Visio

CERTIFICATE & LICENSES

2022	Canada Ontario Driving License (Full G)
2022	HKSAR EMSD Registered Electrical Worker for Electrical Work, Grade C0
2021	Certificate in Building Information Modelling (BIM) Advanced Modelling Course (MEP) – Revit
2018	Certificate in Building Information Modelling (BIM) Basic Modelling Course – Revit
2012	Pearson LCCI Level 2 Certification in Bookkeeping and Accounting